( harmonica wails )
( theme music playing )
( laughs )
OKAY. WE BET $50.000.
- Roseanne: I CALL.
- IT'S NOT YOUR TURN. MOM.
I KNOW.
BUT IT'S MY HOUSE.
WE GONNA PLAY POKER.
OR SHOOT THE BREEZE?
- SHOOT THE BREEZE.
- Dan: OKAY.
THE PORTCHESTER GAME.
LAST GAME OF MY SENIOR YEAR.
- ( kids whining )
- WE'RE DOWN BY A TOUCHDOWN
WITH ONE MINUTE TO GO.
- LET'S PLAY POKER.
- NOW WE GOTTA SHOOT THE BREEZE.
I GET TO TELL THIS STORY.
- DAD. WE KNOW THIS STORY.
- THIS TIME I'M TELLING IT FROM
THE REFEREE'S POINT OF VIEW.
- I GOT A PAIR.
- SO DO I.
YEAH. BUT ROSEANNE'S
ARE SHOWING.
YOU GUYS THINK WE DON'T GET
YOUR CORNY LITTLE SEX JOKES.
HEY. YOU KIDS ARE
OUR CORNY LITTLE SEX JOKES.
( doorbell rings )
GEEZ. IT'S THE FUZZ!
HIDE THE CARDS AND THE JIF!
DARLENE. I THINK
IT'S HIGH TIME
WE TAUGHT D.J. HOW TO
PLAY 52-CARD PICKUP.
( laughing )
( gasps )
TA-DA!
( laughs )
DAD. WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
I CAME TO SEE MY
SWEET LITTLE KAPUSHKA.
- AL!
- HEY. DADDY!
DAD!
OH. MY GOSH!
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- FINE. FINE.
WHERE'S GRANDMA?
- HERE SHE IS NOW.
- HELLO!
MOM!
- MOM. HI.
- AWW.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING IN LANFORD?
WELL. WE GOT UP THIS MORNING
AND I SAID TO YOUR MOTHER.
"WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?"
AND AS USUAL SHE HAD
NO OPINION. SO I SAID.
"LET'S GO FOR A LITTLE RIDE."
TWO HUNDRED AND FIFTY MILES
ISN'T A LITTLE DRIVE.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU HAVE
A WOMAN SITTING NEXT TO YOU
WHO WHENEVER YOU PASS
A CAR SAYS. "I WONDER
WHERE THEY'RE GOING."
BOY. SHE'S GOT PROBLEMS.
MA. WHY DIDN'T
YOU CALL?
I DID. BUT YOUR
LINE WAS BUSY.
THEN I TRIED YOUR SISTER.
I COULDN'T GET A HOLD OF HER.
I THOUGHT MAYBE SOMETHING
WAS WRONG. BUT OF COURSE.
IF THERE WERE. GOD KNOWS.
SHE WOULD NEVER TELL ME.
MY APARTMENT WAS GETTING
FUMIGATED. MOM. SO--
FUMIGATED FOR WHAT?
ALL THOSE LOUSES
YOU GO OUT WITH?
LET ME SEE IF I
GOT THIS STRAIGHT.
- WE NEED MILK--
- MILK.
- WE NEED EGGS.
- EGGS.
BULLETS.
COME ON. DAN. LET'S JUST
TRY TO GET THROUGH THIS.
( sighs )
Roseanne:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
I CAN'T SLEEP.
GRANDPA'S IN THE BATHROOM
MAKING THOSE GAGGING NOISES.
EW.
HOW LONG'S
HE BEEN IN THERE?
AT LEAST
A HALF AN HOUR.
WELL. HE'S PROBABLY
GOT IT ALL UP BY NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU
GO BACK TO BED.
MOM. HE'S REALLY
DRIVING ME CRAZY.
IF HE SAYS "PULL MY FINGER"
ONE MORE TIME--
WELL. NOW YOU KNOW
WHERE I GET MY SMART.
SOPHISTICATED WIT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT MAN RAISED YOU.
NOW YOU KNOW WHY
I WAS SO CRAZY TO
MARRY YOU SO YOUNG.
I THOUGHT IT WAS BECAUSE
YOU WERE MADLY IN LOVE.
YEAH. WITH THE IDEA OF
GETTING OUT OF MY HOUSE.
IS THERE A PLACE
IN HERE TO SIT DOWN?
YEAH. WHY DON'T YOU TRY
ONE OF THESE THINGS
WE CALL "CHAIRS"?
WE SIT IN 'EM
FREQUENTLY.
WHAT KIND OF LIST IS HE MAKING?
NOT THAT IT'S ANY
OF MY BUSINESS.
A HIT LIST.
HE'S JUST GONNA GO
OUT TO THE STORE AND
PICK UP A FEW THINGS.
PLEASE DON'T GET
ANYTHING SPECIAL FOR ME.
I'LL EAT WHATEVER YOU HAVE.
BUT YOUR FATHER'S DIET
IS LOW SODIUM. LOW FAT.
AND HIGH FIBER.
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST GET
HIM SOME WOOD. YOU KNOW?
AND THEN HE CAN PUT MUSTARD
ON IT AND. YOU KNOW.
THAT'D BE A GOOD TREAT.
MUSTARD'S HIGH IN FAT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T KNOW THAT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE
DON'T CARE.
I DO. BUT DOGGONE IT.
I GOTTA GO.
( door closes )
- HE'S NOT WORKING. IS HE?
- HE'S WORKING.
WELL. I'M GLAD.
BECAUSE YOUR FATHER WORRIES.
ESPECIALLY ABOUT
YOUR SISTER.
( sighs )
HE DOESN'T
HAVE TO WORRY.
WELL. SOMEBODY HAS TO.
SHE'S 32. SHE'S UNMARRIED.
HEAVEN FORBID THAT SHE TURNS OUT
TO BE LIKE YOUR AUNT DALE.
WHO TEACHES P.E.
SPEAKING OF AUNT DALE.
HOW IS UNCLE SHIRLEY?
ALSO. YOUR FATHER
IS CONCERNED
BECAUSE YOUR SISTER
LIVES IN A BUILDING
THAT NEEDS
TO BE FUMIGATED.
BUT I AM HER MOTHER.
IT IS NOT MY JOB
TO TELL HER WHAT TO DO.
OH. I GET IT.
BUT IT IS YOUR JOB TO TELL ME
TO TELL HER WHAT TO DO.
YES. I'M SURE PETUNIAS
ARE PERENNIALS.
JACKIE. MOM WAS JUST
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
NOW YOU GET TO LISTEN
WHILE SHE TALKS ABOUT ME.
SO. ARE WE GONNA
TALK ABOUT ROSEANNE?
CERTAINLY NOT.
IT'S JUST THAT YOUR FATHER
IS WORRIED ABOUT HER.
SHE SEEMS SO TIRED
ALL THE TIME.
MAMA...
YOU'VE BEEN HERE
A GRAND TOTAL OF ONE HOUR.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
HOW TIRED SHE IS?
A MOTHER KNOWS.
GRANTED. IT IS
A DIFFERENT GENERATION.
BUT YOUR FATHER
WOULD HAVE DIED BEFORE
HE MADE ME GO OUT TO WORK.
DAN DOESN'T MAKE
ROSEANNE WORK.
THAT'S WHAT
SHE TELLS YOU.
BUT YOU'VE NEVER BEEN MARRIED.
YOU DON'T KNOW THESE THINGS.
WHAT'D YOU FIND OUT
ABOUT ME?
YOU'RE
VERY TIRED.
HEY. MA. IS TWO
BLANKETS ENOUGH?
TWO'S FINE.
IF THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE.
NO. I HAVE MORE.
HOW MANY WOULD YOU LIKE?
WHAT DID
YOUR FATHER SAY?
HE SAYS HE'S GONNA BE SLEEPING
OUT IN THE DRIVEWAY NAKED.
HOW MANY BLANKETS
DO YOU WANT. MA?
IF YOU HAVE TWO.
TWO'S FINE.
I AM THIS CLOSE
TO THE EDGE.
AND IF I GO OVER.
I'M TAKING YOU WITH ME.
SHE DOES HAVE A WAY
ABOUT HER. DOESN'T SHE?
IF SHE WANTS TO RAG ON
YOUR LIFE. WHY DOESN'T
SHE JUST TELL YOU?
I'M GETTING SO SICK OF
THESE BEHIND-THE-BACK
CONVERSATIONS.
YOU MEAN. LIKE THE ONE
WE'RE HAVING ABOUT
MOM RIGHT NOW?
- YEAH.
I MEAN. WHY SHOULD
I HAVE TO DEFEND THE
GUYS YOU GO OUT WITH?
YOU SHOULDN'T.
AND I'M TIRED OF
EXPLAINING TO HER
WHY YOUR HOUSE IS
SO FILTHY ALL THE TIME.
YEAH. THAT'S
MY BUSINESS.
YEAH. SHE JUST
DOESN'T LET UP.
WELL. SHE'S GONNA LET UP.
BECAUSE I'M GONNA LAY INTO HER.
WELL. I'M GONNA
LAY INTO HER TOO.
THAT WOMAN'S NOT QUALIFIED
TO JUDGE ANYBODY'S LIFE.
- WHERE IS SHE?
- MOM?!
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH ALREADY.
WE GOTTA DO THIS.
ABSOLUTELY.
I FOUND THIS UNDER
YOUR SISTER'S SOFA.
MOM. WHY ARE YOU
GIVING IT TO ME?
IT'S HER POTATO CHIPS.
IT'S HER SOFA.
IT'S HER HOUSE.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE THE WAY
THAT ROSEANNE KEEPS HOUSE.
THEN YOU TALK TO
ROSEANNE ABOUT IT.
YOU DON'T TALK TO ME.
AND IF YOU DON'T LIKE
THE WAY THAT I RUN MY LIFE.
THEN YOU TALK TO ME ABOUT IT.
YOU DON'T TALK TO ROSEANNE.
WE'RE-- WE'RE SICK AND TIRED OF
THE WAY THAT YOU MANIPULATE US.
IS THAT SO.
ROSEANNE?
YEAH. RIGHT?
WELL. MAYBE "MANIPULATE"
IS KIND OF A HARSH
WORD TO USE HERE.
I JUST THINK
WHAT JACKIE MEANS.
WHAT SHE'S TRYING TO
SAY IS THAT WE WISH
THAT YOU WOULD JUST
TRY TO DEAL WITH US
IN A MORE DIRECT MANNER.
YOU KNOW.
IF YOU WANT TO.
NO. THAT'S NOT WHAT
JACKIE'S TRYING TO SAY.
WHAT JACKIE'S
TRYING TO SAY--
WHERE THE HELL WERE
YOU FIVE MINUTES AGO?
I'LL GET SOME
SHEETS. MOM.
YOU REALLY SHOULD TURN
YOUR MATTRESS MORE OFTEN.
- WHERE ARE
YOU GUYS GONNA SLEEP?
- ANYWHERE'S OKAY WITH ME.
HEY. I DON'T
SLEEP ANYWHERE.
WELL. THESE COTS
ARE PRETTY NICE.
OH. I'M SURE MOM
AND DAD DON'T WANNA
SLEEP ON ANY COTS.
WHAT DID WE DO
LAST TIME?
I'VE COMPLETELY BLOCKED IT
OUT OF MY MIND.
YOU GUYS DON'T MIND
SLEEPING ON COTS. DO YOU?
I CAN SLEEP
ANYWHERE.
WHY DON'T YOU AND DAD
JUST TAKE ME AND DAN'S BED.
AND WE'LL SLEEP
OUT HERE ON THE COTS?
HONEY. I CAN'T SLEEP
ON THESE THINGS.
LAST TIME DARLENE AND I
SLEPT DOWNSTAIRS ON THE COTS.
AND GRANDMA AND GRANDPA
SLEPT UP IN OUR ROOM.
I WANT TO SLEEP
ON THE SLEEPING BAGS.
NO. THAT'S NOT WHAT
WE DID LAST YEAR.
I'M VERY PARTICULAR
ABOUT WHERE I SLEEP.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING ABOUT ME.
I'LL NEVER SLEEP
IN A COMMUNIST COUNTRY.
I'LL VISIT ONE
DURING THE DAY.
BUT I'LL NEVER SLEEP
IN ONE AT NIGHT.
WELL. GOD BLESS
AMERICA.
- CAN I SLEEP IN
YOUR SLEEPING BAG?
- Roseanne: NO. GO.
HOW ABOUT
WHAT I SAID?
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- FORGET WHAT SHE SAID.
PLEASE. LET'S NOT
FUSS ABOUT THIS.
DAD AND I CAN
SLEEP ANYWHERE.
DARLENE AND I SLEPT
ON THE COTS. AND GRANDMA
AND GRANDPA HAD OUR ROOM.
THESE COTS STILL SMELL
FROM WHEN WE FOUND
THE DEAD PIGEON IN IT.
- DARLENE.
- Jackie: OKAY.
D.J. AND I MUST HAVE
BOTH SLEPT ON THE FLOOR.
MOM AND DAD HAD D.J.'S BED--
BUT THAT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN.
BECAUSE D.J.'S BED'S TOO SMALL
AND THEY WOULD HAVE
BEEN UNCOMFORTABLE.
JACKIE. YOU WERE
NOT EVEN HERE.
TEMPER. TEMPER.
THEN HOW COME
I CAN REMEMBER IT?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TOTAL RECALL OF ALL
THINGS IMAGINARY!
GIRLS. GIRLS.
LET'S BE LADIES.
SHALL WE?
CAN WE COME TO SOME
SORT OF CONCLUSION HERE?
OKAY. YOU WANT A CONCLUSION?
I'LL GIVE YOU A CONCLUSION.
OKAY. JACKIE. YOU GO
SLEEP IN D.J.'S BED.
D.J.. SLEEP IN
A SLEEPING BAG!
GIRLS. GIRLS. GIRLS.
LET'S JUST BE LITTLE LADIES
AND GO UP AND SLEEP
IN YOUR OWN BED.
- MOM AND DAD. YOU TAKE
ME AND DAN'S ROOM.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
AND I'M GONNA
SLEEP HERE ON THE COT.
AND SO IS MR. FLEXIBLE.
HOPEFULLY WE WON'T
HAVE ALL THIS CONFUSION
ONCE YOUR FATHER AND I
HAVE OUR OWN PLACE
RIGHT HERE
IN LANFORD.
SLEEP TIGHT.
EVERYONE.
NIGHTY NIGHT.
DAN. ARE YOU
SLEEPING?
LIKE A BABY.
THE FACT THAT IT'S 4:30
IN THE MORNING AND I HAVE
A SPRING IN MY PANCREAS
ISN'T KEEPING ME AWAKE
THE LEAST LITTLE BIT.
IF MY PARENTS
MOVE TO LANFORD.
I AM GONNA BE SLEEPING
ON A COT FOR THE REST
OF MY LIFE.
BECAUSE I'M GONNA
BE IN PRISON FOR
BLOWING 'EM AWAY.
HONEY. HONEY.
BE REALISTIC.
YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW TO USE A GUN.
I'LL DO IT.
SERIOUSLY. DAN.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WELL. I'D SAY
"LET'S SLEEP ON IT."
BUT WHO CAN SLEEP?!
YOU KNOW. IF YOU KNEW HOW
TO STAND UP TO YOUR PARENTS.
WE WOULDN'T BE
LYING HERE RIGHT NOW.
WHAT IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
AND I'M WARNING YOU. THAT
FIREPLACE POKER'S WITHIN REACH.
BABY. LET'S NOT
GET INTO THIS RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE IT'S NOT MY WARPED.
PSYCHOTIC. NEUROTIC PARENTS
THAT ARE LAYING IN MY BED.
- I'M GONNA GO SIT ON THE PORCH.
- Dan: HONEY. HONEY.
HONEY. LET'S NOT
DO THIS TO EACH OTHER.
COME ON. BABY.
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST ANGRY
'CAUSE I HAVEN'T SLEPT.
WE GOT A COUPLE HOURS
LEFT TILL DAYLIGHT.
LET'S JUST TRY
TO SALVAGE SOME SLEEP.
( crickets chirping )
( Al clears throat )
Mom: AL?
- AL?
- RIGHT HERE.
OH. YOU TWO
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
I'M JUST GONNA MAKE
YOUR FATHER BREAKFAST.
HE ALWAYS GETS UP AT 4:30.
WHY? I DON'T KNOW.
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
FEEL LIKE MAKING LOVE?
DON'T GET UP.
I JUST WANT TO
KNOW WHERE YOU KEEP
YOUR CITRUS FRUIT.
I THINK THERE'S SOME STRAWBERRY
POP-TARTS IN THE FRIDGE.
YOUR FATHER NEEDS TO HAVE
A PIECE OF CITRUS FRUIT.
I THINK THERE'S AN ORANGE
UNDER THE DRYER.
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
DAN SHOULDN'T SLEEP
ON HIS LEFT SIDE.
IT'S BAD FOR THE HEART.
SO'S A RUSTY SPIKE.
THIS IS NUTS.
I GOT A NEW JOB
TO START TODAY.
I'VE GOTTA GO TO
WORK TOO. YOU KNOW.
WELL. WHY DON'T YOU
GO IN THERE AND TELL
MA AND PA KETTLE TO SHUT UP?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP
SO EARLY?
YOU KNOW. THIS IS
THE BEST ROOM IN YOUR HOUSE.
YEAH. 'CAUSE MOM
AND DAD AREN'T IN IT.
THIS IS OUR ONLY
SANCTUARY FROM THEM.
WELL. DON'T
COUNT ON IT.
SHE'LL FIGURE OUT
SOME WAY TO GET IN HERE.
AND THEN YOU CAN
STAND UP TO HERE AGAIN
LIKE YOU DID BEFORE.
I SAID
TO YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
"BEVERLY"--
I CALL HER BEVERLY
BECAUSE THAT'S HER NAME.
I SAID. "BEVERLY.
THIS YEAR I'M GONNA
PAY MORE ATTENTION TO
MY STABLE AND HORSES."
YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY HORSES. GRANDPA.
'CAUSE I DON'T
HAVE A STABLE.
- PULL MY FINGER. KID.
- DON'T.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
OH. I'M FINISHED.
ARE YOU GUYS GETTING
READY FOR SCHOOL?
YEAH. AND WE'RE REALLY
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
THAT'S GREAT.
THEY'RE REALLY DOING
GREAT IN SCHOOL.
AL WAS ALWAYS VERY CONCERNED
WITH THE CHILDREN'S EDUCATION.
HE WAS SOME FATHER.
WHAT IS IT YOU
ALWAYS USED TO SAY?
YOU CAN LEAD
A HORSE TO WATER.
BUT YOU CAN'T
MAKE 'EM THINK.
YOU USED TO SAY THAT?
AND YOU STOPPED
SAYING THAT?
HE USED TO SAY THAT.
AND HE DOESN'T
SAY IT ANYMORE.
HE USED TO SAY.
"YOU CAN LEAD
A HORSE TO WATER.
BUT YOU CAN'T
MAKE 'EM THINK."
AND HE DOESN'T
SAY IT ANYMORE.
I HAVEN'T SLEPT.
I SWEAR WE'RE
ONLY SANE TODAY
BECAUSE WE KEPT
EACH OTHER THAT WAY.
I KNOW. WE PROTECTED
EACH OTHER FROM MR.
AND MRS. TOTAL INSANITY.
YEAH. LIKE THAT TIME THAT
YOU WERE IN THE EIGHTH GRADE
AND YOU WERE DATING
THAT 40-YEAR-OLD GUY.
- AAH!
- HE WAS NOT 40.
OH. HE WAS THE ONLY GUY
AT YOUR FRESHMAN DANCE
THAT WAS
WEARING A TOUPEE.
I TOLD MOM
HE WAS YOUR TUTOR.
AND I TAUGHT HIM
MORE THAN HE TAUGHT ME.
WELL. THAT'S
THE WAY IT GOES.
THE BOTTOM LINE
IS THAT
MOM AND DAD ARE
JUST SO OUT THERE.
WELL. YOU KNOW.
IT'S NOT ALL THEIR FAULT.
WE SHOULD SHOW 'EM
A LITTLE COMPASSION.
WELL. HERE
WE GO AGAIN.
CHECKING YOUR BACKBONE
AT THE DOOR.
WELL. FINE.
YOU BLAME YOUR
WHOLE LIFE--
OH. ROSEANNE.
YOU TURN INTO
A LITTLE ROBOT
EVERY TIME MOM
AND DAD COME AROUND.
YOU TURN INTO LITTLE ROSIE
TWO-SHOES. AND I'M SICK OF IT.
HEY. PEOPLE WHO LIVE IN
COCKROACH-INFESTED APARTMENTS
SHOULD NOT THROW STONES.
- I CAN'T EVEN TALK TO YOU!
- OH. SHUT UP!
YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO GET YOUR OWN WAY.
IT HAS TO BE MY WAY
WHEN YOU'RE STANDING
HERE IN MY BATHROOM
AT 7:30 IN THE MORNING
AFTER MY PARENTS CAME OVER
TO MY HOUSE AND DECIMATE
MY WHOLE FAMILY.
NOW THEY'RE YOUR
PARENTS. FINE.
IF YOU WANT 'EM.
FINE. YOU HAVE 'EM!
GEE. YOU TELL ME WHEN
IT'S THEIR ANNIVERSARY.
- AND YOU LET 'EM STAY AT YOUR
HOUSE NEXT TIME THEY COME...
- FINE. GOOD.
AND DECIMATE YOUR WHOLE FAMILY.
OF WHICH YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE.
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T CONCENTRATE
ON NOTHING LONG ENOUGH THAN
IT TAKES TO CHUG A BEER!
AND DON'T GIVE ME THAT WOUNDED
LITTLE JACKIE LOOK EITHER.
BECAUSE THAT ONLY WORKS ON GUYS
NAMED MIKE WHO DRIVE EL CAMINOS.
VERY DRAMATIC.
ROSEANNE.
OH. SO NOW YOU'RE
NOT GONNA TALK TO ME.
GOD. WOULD I LOVE TO
THROW A HAMMER THROUGH
A PLATE GLASS WINDOW.
DON'T WAIT FOR
A RESPONSE. DAN.
HER MAJESTY'S
NOT SPEAKING TO
ANYBODY TODAY.
- JACKIE. WHO EVEN ASKED YOU?
- HEY. I'M A PART OF
THIS FAMILY TOO.
YEAH. WHEN YOUR HAMPER'S FULL
OR YOUR CAR NEEDS WORKING ON.
I'VE BEEN A MEMBER OF THIS
FAMILY LONGER THAN YOU HAVE!
( laughing )
BOY. THAT'S SOMETHING
TO BE PROUD OF!
YOU KNOW. I SAW A WHOLE THING
ABOUT THIS ON OPRAH.
AND THAT'S
JUST WHAT WE ARE TOO.
WE'RE JUST LIKE THAT.
WE ARE A DYSFUNCTIONAL FAMILY!
( screams )
THANKS. GRAMPS.
BYE. GRAM.
- Al: BYE. BECKY.
- Beverly: BYE. DEAR.
GRANDPA SAID HE'D BUY ME
A HORSE NEXT YEAR.
YEAH. WELL. GRANDPA'S
SADDLE'S ON TOO TIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M MAKING BREAKFAST
FOR MY KIDS.
I ALREADY MADE
THEM BREAKFAST.
GO TO SCHOOL THEN.
- BYE.
- Al: BYE. KIDS.
YEAH. SHE MADE 'EM BREAKFAST.
CEREAL AND CHOCOLATE
CHIP COOKIES.
YOUR FATHER GAVE
THEM THE COOKIES.
WHETHER THEY EAT 'EM
NOW OR IN THE AFTERNOON.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE DIFFERENCE?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
THE DIFFERENCE IS.
YOU SHOW UP AT MY DOOR
UNANNOUNCED. UNINVITED.
YOU JUST DRIVE EVERYBODY
AND WORK 'EM UP INTO A FRENZY
UNTIL WE'RE READY
TO KILL EACH OTHER!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE HAVING A NICE BREAKFAST.
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
IF YOU GUYS ARE GONNA
MOVE HERE TO LANFORD.
YOU HAVE GOT TO MOVE
ONTO THE WHOLE OTHER
SIDE OF THIS TOWN.
BECAUSE I AM NOT GONNA
BE ABLE TO TAKE THIS
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
WHO'S MOVING
TO LANFORD?
YOU GUYS ARE.
YOU SAID SO LAST NIGHT.
OH. WE'RE NEVER GONNA
MOVE INTO LANFORD.
WE WERE JUST THINKING.
WE WERE JUST TALKING.
WHY DO YOU TAKE
EVERYTHING SO SERIOUSLY?
SO YOU'RE
NOT MOVING?
NO. IN FACT.
WE'VE GOT TO GET GOING.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY TO
SEE COUSIN SYDNEY
IN BEAUFORD.
HE HAD GUM SURGERY.
I'M GONNA BUY HIM
SOME ROCK CANDY.
WELL. IT'S A SHAME
YOU COULDN'T STAY LONGER.
DAN. DO YOU REALLY
MEAN THAT?
HEY. IF YOU DON'T THINK
YOU GUYS LEAVING IS
GONNA AFFECT EVERYBODY.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
AL. DID YOU HEAR THAT?
YEAH. I'D GIVE HIM
A BIG KISS...
- OH.
- ...IF I LIKED BOYS.
OH. MOM. I'M REALLY
GONNA MISS YOU.
ME TOO.
BIG HUG.
THIS HAS BEEN
A GREAT VISIT.
OH. THIS HAS BEEN
A WONDERFUL VISIT.
Al:
LET ME DO IT AGAIN.
AND THE SICK THING IS
THAT I KIND OF MISS 'EM.
I KIND OF DON'T.
DAN?
WHAT-EE?
PULL MY FINGER.
AAH!
Dan: HERE'S THE DEAL.
I'LL GET THE CHECKBOOK OUT.
BUT I GOTTA WATCH.
- HEY. WHAT A SURPRISE.
- I WAS GUNNA DO THE LINE.
WELL. I'M NOT WORKING.
SO I THOUGHT I'D COME
OVER AND GET SOME LINES.
I'M GONNA GET
OUT OF HERE.
HOW NICE.
THAT WAS FUN.